Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series CV. 1951 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 517-254. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 254
    - Organizing activities of System Boards and Local Lodges, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 517-255. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 255
    - Reduce loss and damage claims, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 517-256. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 256
    - Consolidation of transportation agencies, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 517-257. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 257
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 622a, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 517-258. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 258
    - Amendment of United States Code, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 517-259. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 259
    - Safety requirements for natural gas pipelines, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 517-260. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 260
    - Reestablish Express Boards of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 517-261. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 261
    - Retirement at age 60 or after 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 517-262. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 262
    - Free transportation for employees of Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 517-263. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 263
    - 15 days' vacation after 10 years' service, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 517-264. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 264
    - Restore 7-day assignments, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 517-265. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 265
    - Reduce vacation hours for furloughed employees from 2032 to 750, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 517-266. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 266
    - Delegates required to pay railroad fare to convention to be refunded costs, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 517-267. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 267
    - More effective and prompter handling of grievances, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 517-268. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 268
    - Funds and securities of System Boards of Adjustment, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 517-269. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 269
    - 80-90% of jobs below Class I to be assigned as regular assigned jobs, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 517-270. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 270
    - Revise Rules Agreement with Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 517-271. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 271
    - Amend Selective Service Act to properly protect employment rights of returning servicemen, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 517-272. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 272
    - Amend Retirement Act to provide earlier retirement age and more adequate benefits, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 517-273. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 273
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act to provide that a widow, married at least 10 years, receive 75% of pension to which her husband was entitled, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 517-274. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 274
    - Retirement at age 60 or after 30 years' service, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 517-275. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 275
    - Compulsory retirement age to be reduced to 60, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 517-276. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 276
    - Retirement after 30 years' service regardless of age; increase sick and retirement benefits by 25%, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 517-277. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 277
    - Oppose policy of Railroad Retirement Board requiring applicants for sick benefits to give information about their race or color, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 517-278. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 278
    - Earlier retirement age and more adequate benefits, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 517-279. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 279
    - Lower retirement age to 60, with full benefits after 30 years; increase pension benefits, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 517-280. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 280
    - National Sick Leave Agreement providing 10 days each year without restriction, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 517-281. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 281
    - Express Messengers to be transferred with their work to over-the-road truck service, with seniority rights unimpaired, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 517-282. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 282
    - Negotiate Agreement providing for a 6-hour day Monday through Friday, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 517-283. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 283
    - National Agreement providing free hospitalization for employees, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 517-284. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 284
    - Reduce vacation hours of furloughed employees from 2032 to 750, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 517-285. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 285
    - Railway Express Agency to provide hospitalization; also carry $3000 life insurance policy on each employee; pay additional $50 per month to pensioners, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 517-286. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 286
    - Grievances. Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 517-287. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 287
    - Free transportation for employees of Railway Express Agency, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 517-288. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 288
    - When Railway Express Agency pay day falls on Saturday, Sunday, or holiday, employees to be paid the day before, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 517-289. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 289
    - Amend Unemployment Insurance Act to liberalize unemployment and sickness benefits, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 517-290. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 290
    - Payment for holidays for all groups represented by Brotherhood, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 517-291. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 291
    - Sick leave and holiday pay for all railroad workers, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 517-292. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 292
    - Guaranteed living annual wage, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 517-293. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 293
    - 15 days' vacation for employees with 6-19 years' service; 20 days for 20-29 years' 30 days for 30 or more years, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 517-294. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 294
    - Negotiate National Sick Leave Agreement permitting sick leave time to be accumulated up to 90 days, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 517-295. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 295
    - Amend Railway Labor Act to speed up wage negotiations., 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 517-296. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 296
    - Negotiate Agreement providing pay for holidays, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 517-297. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 297
    - All Agreements entered into be made subject to ratification of Local Lodges, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 517-298. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 298
    - Liberalize benefits provided for in National Vacation Agreement, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 517-299. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 299
    - 5 days' vacation after 1 year's service; 10 days after 5-10 years; thereafter 1 additional day for each year, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 517-300. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 300
    - Improve foreign line trip passes on national basis, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 517-301. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 301
    - Better cooperation and coordination of efforts of Lodges and System Boards; rescind Resolution No. 163 on page 123 of Grand Lodge Constitution, effective July 1, 1947, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 517-302. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 302
    - Pay for recognized holidays, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 517-303. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 303
    - Carriers be required to pay employees when required to render jury service, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 517-304. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 304
    - Negotiate National Sick Leave Agreement, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 517-305. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 305
    - 3 days' leave of absence with pay for death in family, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 517-306. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 306
    - Increase sickness and unemployment benefits under Unemployment Insurance Act, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 517-307. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 307
    - 15 days' vacation after 3 years' service, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 517-308. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 308
    - Members are ineligible to become Lodge officers and committeemen if delinquent in dues or engaged in illegal gambling activities or illegal money lending, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 517-309. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 309
    - 7 legal holidays with pay; time and one-half if worked, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 517-310. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 310
    - Paid holidays for all employees covered by our Agreements, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 517-311. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 311
    - Negotiate Sick Leave Agreement with railroads providing for payment for first day of illness to the end of period not covered by Unemployment Insurance Act, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 517-312. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 312
    - Reduction of Parcel Post weight and size, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 517-313. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 313
    - Free transportation for Railway Express Agency employees, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 517-314. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 314
    - Consolidations, transfer or dissolution of work or facilities, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 517-315. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 315
    - Assure Express employees the right to all express work on trains, trucks, buses, terminal points where Railway Express Agency subcontracts it or uses trainmen to perform Express Agency work, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 517-316. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 316
    - Retain segregation of Group I and II employees, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 517-317. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 317
    - Sponsor legislation limiting size of trucks, speed; maintain adequate brakes, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 517-318. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 318
    - Inaugurate wage-increase movement when opportunity arises, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 517-319. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 319
    - Inaugurate a movement to provide paid holidays, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 517-320. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 320
    - Negotiate Sick Leave Rule providing pay for all time lost, 1951-1952 (Box 622a, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 517-321. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 321
    - No discrimination in free transportation on account of race, creed or color, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 517-322. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 322
    - Abolish restriction on all free transportation annual passes, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 517-323. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 323
    - No discrimination between white and colored mail and baggage handlers, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 517-324. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 324
    - 3 weeks' vacation for employees with 15 or more years' seniority, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 517-325. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 325
    - Foreign relations., 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 517-326. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 326
    - Approve foreign policy, 1951-1957 (Box 622a, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 517-327. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 327
    - Free transportation for widows of deceased employees, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 517-328. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 328
    - Equalization of wage rates, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 517-329. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 329
    - Railway Express Agency employees to be accorded same free transportation privileges as railroad employees, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 517-330. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 330
    - Refrain from participation in legislation concerning rates applying to Parcel Post, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 517-331. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 331
    - Payroll deduction of Union Shop dues and assessments, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 517-332. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 332
    - Lodge Officers ineligible to serve if engaged in illegal activities or illegal money lending, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 517-333. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 333
    - Rescind action requiring annual System Board meeting, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 517-334. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 334
    - Combine roster of Express Messengers and over-the-road truck employees, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 517-335. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 335
    - 80-90 percent of jobs below Class I be set as regular assigned jobs, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 517-336. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 336
    - Express appreciation to City of San Francisco, California, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 517-337. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 337
    - Express appreciation for Pullman refunds, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 517-338. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 338
    - Express appreciation to hotels, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 517-339. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 339
    - Express appreciation to Southern Pacific Railway, Union Pacific Railway, Chicago and Northwestern Railway, Santa Fe Railway and other railroads for special equipment to Convention, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 517-340. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 340
    - Revise National Vacation Agreement to provide a maximum of 20 days per year, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 517-341. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 341
    - Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Acts, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 517-342. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 342
    - Policy on Resolutions., 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 517-343. 1951 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 343
    - Remove restrictions on issuance of foreign line free transportation passes, 1951 (Box 622a, Folder 93)